offerslook.com 2016-08-06

# Performance Marketing Software by Offerslook | Build Your Own Affiliate Network | Build Your Own Ad Network

Last Updated: December 08, 2015

Thank you for visiting the Offerslook™ website located at www.offerslook.com (the "Site") – property of MAAS PVT. LIMITED, a Hong Kong corporation ("Offerslook," "we" or "us"). MAAS PVT. LIMITED is committed to protecting the privacy of our visitors’ personal data. This Privacy Policy relates solely to the Offerslook website and product. 

We provide this privacy policy ("Privacy Policy") in order to explain our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is used by us on our Site www.offerslook.com and through our Offerslook platform. The use of information collected through our service shall be limited to the purpose of providing the service for which the Client has engaged MAAS PVT. LIMITED. You must agree to this Privacy Policy, in its entirety, including our use of cookies in order to: a) access or use our Site; and/or (b) subscribe to any of the Offerslook affiliate network management products and/or services (the "Services") offered on the Site (each, a "Subscription"). Your acceptance of both this Privacy Policy and our use of cookies on the Site shall be deemed a blanket acceptance of such Privacy Policy and cookie usage for all future attempts to access the Site and/or any Subscription of the Services. If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy in its entirety, you are not authorized to become a subscriber ("Subscriber") to the Services and/or use the Site in any manner or form whatsoever. 

If you have questions or complaints regarding our privacy policy or practices, please contact us at [support@offerslook.com.](mailto:support@offerslook.com)

**Privacy Policies Used in Connection with Your Subscription.**

Potential affiliates that sign up for the affiliate program that you establish by and through the Services do so from links on your website or via a Uniform Resource Locator ("URL") supplied to you via the Services (collectively, "Subscription Website"). Such affiliates’ information is stored on the password-protected portal established by and through the Services. Offerslook will not access the affiliate information stored on your password-protected portal unless you specifically request that we do so. You are solely responsible for choosing, and uploading to applicable areas of your Subscription Website, a privacy policy to govern your affiliate program, in which conspicuous written notice is given to internet users who access your Subscription Website ("Subscription Users") that cookies may be used to collect anonymous traffic data, and for which you receive consent prior to placing cookies on the internet device of any such Subscription User. Offerslook is in no way responsible for the collection, storage, use and/or distribution of any data that is submitted by and through your Subscription Website. 

**Personal Data Collection**

We collect personal data on the Site when you attempt to become a Subscriber or otherwise choose to provide personal data to us. Personal data may include, but is not limited to: name, business entity name and/or your title with the applicable business entity, as well as your personal and/or business entity related e-mail address, mailing address, daytime and/or cellular telephone numbers, fax number, credit card and/or any other information requested on the applicable Subscriber registration form. 

**Non-Personal Data Collection**

We may automatically collect and store in log files certain non-personal data about you when you visit many of the Site’s pages, such as the type of browser you are using (e.g., Chrome, Mozilla, or Internet Explorer), the type of operating system you are using, (e.g., Windows or Mac OS) and the domain name of your Internet service provider. We use the non-personal data that we collect to improve the design and content of the Site and to enable us to personalize your Internet experience. We also may use this data in the aggregate to analyze Site usage. We do not link this automatically collected data to other information we collect about you. 

**Social Media (Features) & Widgets**

Our Site includes Social Media Features, such as the Facebook Like button and Widgets, such as the Share this button or interactive mini-programs that run on our Site. These Features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our Site, and may set a cookie to enable the Feature to function properly. Social Media Features and Widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Site. Your interactions with these Features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it. 

**Authentication via Facebook Connect & other OpenID providers**

We may build sections on the Site using sign-in services such as Facebook Connect or an Open ID provider. These services will authenticate your identity and provide you the option to share certain personal information with us such as your name and email address to pre-populate our sign up form. Services like Facebook Connect give you the option to post information about your activities on this Site to your profile page to share with others within your network. 

**Tracking Technologies**

To enhance your experience with the Site, we use "cookies." You cannot use this Site or the Services without agreeing to accept the cookies that we use with the Site. Cookies are small packets of data stored on your computer. Cookies are used by your computer’s browser to store your preferences. Cookies, by themselves, do not tell us your e-mail address or other personal data about you. We use cookies to understand Site usage and to improve the content and offerings on the Site. You may set your browser to warn you that cookies are in use, or to block the use of cookies. Most browsers are set to accept cookies. If your browser is not set to accept cookies, certain uses of the Site may require you to go to your browser user preferences to enable cookies. Each browser is different, so check the "Help" menu of your browser to learn how to change your cookie preferences. If you change computers, operating systems or browsers, or use multiple computers or browsers, you will need to repeat this process for each computer and each browser. To find out more about cookies, please visit www.cookiecentral.com. We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personal information you submit while on our Site. 

We and our third party tracking utility partner collect data using tracking technologies such as Web beacons (which are commonly referred to in the industry as web bugs, pixel tags or Clear GIFs), cookies, scripts, and tags. We do not tie the information gathered by clear gifs to our customers’ personal data. Web beacons are electronic images that may be used on the Site, in our Services, or in our emails to deliver cookies, count visits and determine if an email has been opened and acted upon. These technologies are used in analyzing trends, administering the Site, tracking users’ movements around the Site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. We may receive reports based on the use of these technologies by these companies on an individual as well as aggregated basis. 

We use Local Storage (HTML5), and our third party utility partner uses Local Shared Objects (Flash cookies) and Local Storage (HTML5) to store content information and preferences, and to display advertising based on your web browsing activity. Various browsers may offer their own management tools for removing HTML5. To manage Flash, please click

here: http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager07.html 

**Use of Personal Data**

Offerslook collects information under the direction of its Clients, and has no direct relationship with the individuals whose personal data it processes. We collect information for our clients, if you are a customer of one of our Clients and would no longer like to be contacted by one of our Clients that use our service, please contact the client that you interact with directly. 

We use your personal data in the following ways: (a) to send you information regarding Offerslook and your Subscription to the Services; (b) to track your compliance with the Offerslook Services Agreement ("Services Agreement"); and/or (c) for validation, suppression, content improvement and feedback purposes. You agree that we may contact you at any time with updates and/or any other information that we may deem appropriate for you to receive in connection with your continued use of the Services and request for information regarding additional Offerslook products and/or services. 

**Data Sharing**

As a general rule, and other than in connection with the limited exceptions set forth below, Offerslook will not sell, share or rent your personal data to or with others. 

Notwithstanding the foregoing, Offerslook may, from time to time, provide personal data to certain third-party administrative vendors for credit card processing, offering customer service, efficiency purposes in providing administrative or program management services in connection with your Subscription to the Services such as billing and delivery. Any third-party vendor so used has agreed to protect the confidentiality of information provided by Offerslook. 

Offerslook may transfer personal information to companies that help us provide our service. Transfers to subsequent third parties are covered by the provisions in this Policy regarding notice and choice and the service agreements with our Clients. 

Further, Offerslook reserves the right to share your personal data: (a) where required by law, such as to comply with a subpoena or requested by a court of competent jurisdiction, when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request; (b) in the event of any reorganization, merger, sale, joint venture, assignment, transfer or other disposition of all or any portion of Offerslook’s business, assets or stock, in which case you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Site of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information; (c) where you are in violation of this Privacy Policy, and/or Services Agreement; (d) in the case of a dispute; or (e) where Offerslook determines, in its sole discretion, that such disclosure is necessary to protect the rights of Offerslook and/or a third party, or necessary to protect Offerslook from liability of any kind. The aforementioned includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection. 

**Testimonials and Forums**

We display personal testimonials of satisfied customers on our Site in addition to other endorsements. With your consent we may post your testimonial along with your name. If you wish to update or delete your testimonial, you can contact us at [support@offerslook.com.](mailto:support@offerslook.com)

Our Site offers publicly accessible community forums. You should be aware that any information you provide in this area may be read, collected, and used by others who access it. To request removal of your personal information from our community forum, contact us at [support@offerslook.com.](mailto:support@offerslook.com) In some cases, we may not be able to remove your personal information, in which case we will let you know if we are unable to do so and why. 

**Data Retention**

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. If you wish to cancel your account or request that we no longer use your information to provide you services contact us at [support@offerslook.com.](mailto:support@offerslook.com) We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements. 

**Third Party Links**

The Site may contain links to third-party websites ("Third Party Websites"). Please be aware that Offerslook is not responsible for the privacy practices of Third Party Websites. We encourage you to be aware when you leave the Site and to read the privacy policies of each and every website that collects personal information. This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by the Site. 

**Minors**

Offerslook will never knowingly collect any personal information about individuals under eighteen (18) years of age. If Offerslook obtains actual knowledge that it has collected personal information about an individual under eighteen (18) years of age, that information will be immediately deleted from our platform. Pursuant to our Terms of Service and this Privacy Policy, our customers may not use any Offerslook service in a manner that does not comply with law. For the purposes of this provision, the definitions of "personal information" and "children" (and their translational and linguistic equivalents) are defined by the jurisdiction where the Customer is operating. 

**Your Employees**

Your acceptance of the terms of this Privacy Policy, in their entirety, shall inure to your employees, if any. You agree that any employee who accesses your Account, or who visits the Site under the scope of such employee’s employment with you (and any third party to whom you give rightful access to your Account or Site) agrees to the terms of this Privacy Policy, including, without limitation, our use of cookies and/or web beacons. 

**Security**

We endeavor to safeguard and protect our users’ data. When users submit personal data at the Site, their personal data is protected both online and offline. When our registration process asks users to submit Sensitive Data (such as bank account information and login credentials), and when we transmit such Sensitive Data, that Sensitive Data is encrypted and protected with SSL encryption software. While we use SSL encryption to protect Sensitive Data online, we protect all other user data online and offline We have security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of personal data under our control. Please be advised that, although we take every reasonable precaution available to protect your data, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. Therefore, we cannot warrant that your data will be absolutely secure. Any transmission of data at or through our Site is at your own risk. However, access to your personal data is strictly limited, and not accessible to the public. Only employees, and third party agents, that need the data to perform a specific job are granted access to personal data. Our employees are dedicated to ensuring the security and privacy of all user data. Employees not adhering to our written firm policies are subject to disciplinary action. In compliance with applicable laws, we shall notify you and any applicable regulatory agencies in the event that we learn of an data security breach with respect to your personal data. You will be notified via e-mail in the event of such a breach. Please be advised that notice may be delayed in order to address the needs of law enforcement, determine the scope of network damage, and to engage in remedial measures. You acknowledge that you provide your personal data to Offerslook with knowledgeable consent and at your own risk. 

**Access**

Deleting & Updating Your Information 

If you would like to delete or update the personal information that we have collected from you, simply send your request via e-mail to: [support@offerslook.com.](mailto:support@offerslook.com) We will respond to your access request within 30 days. We will process your request, where possible and subject to the terms and conditions contained herein, within a reasonable period of time after receipt. To protect your privacy and security, we will take reasonable steps to help verify your identity before granting access or making corrections. 

Email Opt-Out 

You may at any time choose to stop receiving emails containing general information regarding Offerslook and/or Offerslook by following the instructions at the end of each such email or by contacting us at [support@offerslook.com.](mailto:support@offerslook.com) There may be a short delay of up to several business days while your request is being verified, deployed and processed across our servers. Notwithstanding the foregoing, we may continue to contact you for the purpose of communicating information relating to your Subscription to the Services, as well as to respond to any inquiry or request made by you. 

Data Controlled by our Clients 

Offerslook has no direct relationship with the individuals whose personal data it processes. An individual who seeks access, or who seeks to correct, amend, or delete inaccurate data should direct his or her query to the Offerslook Client in question (the data controller). If the Client requests Offerslook to remove the data, we will respond to their request within 30 business days. 

**Notification of Changes.**

We may update this privacy policy to reflect changes to our information practices. If we make any material changes we will notify you by email (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on this Site prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices. 

**Contact Us.**

If you have any questions regarding this Privacy Policy, or would like more information on our privacy practices, please contact us at: [support@offerslook.com.](mailto:support@offerslook.com)

MAAS PVT. LIMITED  
Unit 1001 Fourseas Building  
208-212 Nathan Road, Kowloon, Hong Kong
